Pinky finger is standing up.
He's so cute.
I can't remember.
I drink 12 bottles a day already.
Graffiti of youth, any day now
Paint it in high contrast
I can't remember the live Setori!
I'm with you so much.
I'm writing so much here.
I'm writing here.
I'm getting so mad at you for writing here.
I'm getting a lot of flashes of it on the news feeds and stuff,
I get scolded by the manager,
But I can't remember.
I can't remember.
In the beginning, we were all saying to each other, "What's next?
We used to whisper to each other, "What's next?
Now it's just me.
Now it's just me. I'm wondering what's next, and everyone is in their positions,
I'm like, "What am I going to do now?
I totally understand.
I was wondering what was next, and then the next song started,
It's like, "Oh my God, I'm so confused.
Or one of them moves.
I'm afraid of the adults' eyes.
I was afraid of the adults' eyes,
I'm also afraid of the members' eyes.
I write down all the MCs and what I'm going to say,
I write everything down.
What do you write with?
Eyeliner.
After all, it's smudged and I can't see it.
Did you write it down?
Wait, were you writing?
I was.
We're all the same.
I've never seen anyone write before.
Really? Then how are you doing it?
It's in my brain.
Brain?
Input.
But you can't remember, can you?
Not at all.
Really?
But if I write it down, the adults will be scared, and the members will be scared,
It's impossible, isn't it?
How can I remember?
Maybe I've been doing that lately. I've been doing that lately. I've been abbreviating words from the top to the bottom.
The top word.
I see.
It's like the 100 poems.
I don't know all of them.
How should I say it?
I mean, song titles that are connected vertically make strange sentences,
I'm trying to use the anky method.
Is it working?
Yes, it's working.
I'll give it a try.
It's been fine lately.
So, if the first song is "Katsu Ten Ume," the second song is "Taco Rice," and the third song is "Hamburger," you're going to remember it as "Carter's"?
I have an image in my head. Winning is winning. Win.
You remember that, don't you?
You remember "octopus" as "octopus wins. Like that.
The octopus wins! That's how you think.
How do you know?
Maybe we are of the same senses.
I remember Japanese, too, and I memorized a lot of history and vocabulary.
It's the best way to remember.
Yes, I remember "Akari" and "Rig-foot".
That kind of thing.
We're the same! Same!
Wait a minute. I can't keep up. What do you mean?
I'm learning by feel.
If you learn it like that, you'll learn it as the "katsutako" school of thought. If you learn it like that, you'll learn it as a "katsutako" group.
I totally understand.
That's it.
That's how I remember it.
Okay, well, I'll try to remember it once with drinks.
In that order.
Water, you know, it's like se...Water is like a sound effect.
The live image?
The water is the grandmother.
Grandma?
Grandma!
I mean SE.
Oh, I see.
You call an SE a grandma.
So that's how it is.
So the stage we are standing on, this is water.
It is water.
So, the first thing the SE said was that there was a bird near the water.
Yes, yes, yes.
A bird drinking water.
Then we learned a song called "Oolong Tea.
Next was iced coffee.
The water hardened and turned into ice, so we went ice skating.
I was tired from ice skating, so we took a break and MC.
Bird-san took a break.
Then, the next time, I got tired of ice skating, so I took a break and MC'd.
There were people who came to the show.
I, I, I, I. Like orange juice.
And Co was like, "Korra! Like that.
Yes, like that. Kola! Like that.
They got together and were like, "No, you can't do that.
I got together, too, but I gave it back. You know, like, "Hey!
It's my place.
Hey! Hey!
Hey! I'd get a little tingle,
I'd get all hot and bothered.
You got hit, didn't you? It hurts.
It hurts.
I said, "It hurts," and I was probably here one more time,
I said, "That hurts." And then, "Well, I guess the MC got stuck here one more time.
How much MC can fit in there?
MC. It's going to get stuck, so let's get you fixed up.
Is it healed?
Healed.
We were rewarded with a melon at the end of the show.
That's good!
Isn't it great?
Nash!
I have no idea!
I'd be in trouble if I did this in my head.
With this navidad.
Okay, let's write it down now.
With eyeliner?
Use your eyeliner.
Okay.
I'm so fascinated by this live video.
What should I do with it? It's a tough decision.
I was really taken by it, and I wanted to show it to everyone.
I really have that kind of thing.
I was so taken by the image of Airi Suzuki at the Budokan for Aono-san's "Hatsukoi Cider".
No way. You're going to see Airi Suzuki?
It's the best.
Let's take a look.
Wow, she's amazing.
She's so beautiful.
Her pinky finger is standing up.
She's so cute.
She has such a powerful voice that all the people are already attracted to her,
And her looks are too good to be true.
I've been doing this for a long time, and I think it's amazing that she can sing so well a cappella,
It's really amazing.
It's really amazing. Really wonderful.
I really love it,
I saw Yui on TikTok with Airi Suzuki,
I saw it, I saw it.
Wait for me.
Look.
Look at me too.
I was looking at it so hard.
Can I ask you to take a look?
Sure.
Isn't she really cute?Seriously, isn't he cute?
Shall we watch TikTok once?
Once TikTok.
That's right.
This is bad, isn't it?
This feeling.
It was bad.
I was standing just now.
It's zero centimeters, right?
Zero centimeters.
And this song, Fruit Zipper, is from my group,
They were dancing so perfectly.
He memorized it.
She was so cute.
Usually, high tone is cute.
Amazing.
How did this come about?
I had mentioned it to her as a fan on my own,
I had never performed with her before, and this was the first time we performed together, and she took this picture of me.
It was the moment that made me feel happy to be an idol. I was so happy.
I was really happy.
I loved it.
I felt honored.
What did you talk about?
Please give me information not shown here.
I was told that I was kind of smitten.
She watched a lot of videos of the show,
I was so happy to hear that Ailee said she had a crush on him too.
It's too nice.
I feel like I'm going to fall over. To hear her say that from this distance, right in front of me.
I felt like I had achieved my biggest goal in life, or rather, my dream came true.
What do you bring backstage that makes you excited?
The theme of the talk has flown away, hasn't it?
That's right.
What do you bring backstage that makes you excited?
It's not often that I get a chance to talk about it out in the open,
So I thought I'd ask a nasty question,
I chose this one.
I chose this one. It's an energy drink,
Nutritional drink?
The theme of the live show is that the live show is a riot,
We are a 4-member group that dances and sings like crazy,
But when we do Nutri-Drink, it's like, "Okay, let's go! The live performance was a lot of fun,
I feel like I can perform very powerfully at the live show,
I have a feeling like that,
So, I think it's a good thing that I have a nutritional drink. I think that makes Kismet very happy,
I think it makes Kismet very happy.
Is the camera here?
Please, everyone!
Bye-kisses!
Nutritional drink.
I'll bring it.
On the contrary, do you drink nutritional drinks?
I do.
Drink? You drink it?
Something like Chocola BB.
Ahhh...
Vitamins.
I know what you mean.
You seem to have a lot of them, like 10 bottles.
In a bag.
What about you, Nanako?
I have oranamisin.
Oh, Olanamisin?
I only drink Olanamisin.
Oh, really?
I drink 12 bottles a day.
Twelve?
That's right. But, you know, that's not good.
Of course it is.
I'm fine. I have one or two now.
But you love it so much.
I love it.
Is it for vitamin C or something?
Why don't the three of us make a pact?
Like giving you this.
Backstage next time we see each other?
Yeah.
So, are you full?
Yes, I am.I am now in the process of getting a new one.
Pappan!
I was really, really nervous at first,
I wondered if I would be able to speak,
I was wondering if I'd be able to talk, but... I saw it like this.
We got along so well that I didn't think we would.
The last page of the menu.
Thank you very much for the special private talk.
As a closing sweet,
What if these three were in the same group?
and take potential photos on the theme.
Thank you very much for coming to our restaurant today.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What would you do?
What would you do if these three people were in the same group?
What do you think, like a pose or something?
What kind of theme for the idol group?
Did I hear something today? Word.
Hitomishiri.
Team Hitomishiri.
Hitomishiri,
But..,
Hitomishiri, but..,
But only to those who support us,
we can convey our feelings to only those who support us.
We are such an idol.
That's the theme.
It's early.
Long.
Are you okay with that?
Are you okay with that? This theme.
What should I do with the pose?
Showing off your nimbleness.
Appealing to people's attention.
Something like this.
It's nice.
It's going to be popular.
I'm hiding it.
You're aiming for yakiniku, right?
You go out for ramen and break up right away,
Then, we'll go to yakiniku next.
Yakiniku is nice.
But even yakiniku is still a bit difficult for me.
High?
I think the self-service type is the last thing I want to do.
Let's make a schedule.
Let's make it like we're aiming for the Budokan,
Like we're aiming for the Budokan, or like we're aiming for Yakiniku,
Maybe even Yakiniku style.
Yakiniku style.
It's getting really difficult.
Is this what you mean?
It's so lame.
Wouldn't this be better?
Do you want a double?
You mean use these?
Don't push!
Oh, my God!
This is so good!
If I'm still a senior...
Please subscribe to our channel!